{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a transport layer vulnerability?",
      "options": [
        "Mishandling of undefined, poorly defined",
        "The Vulnerability that allows “fingerprinting” & other enumeration of host information",
        "Overloading of transport-layer mechanisms",
        "Unauthorized network access"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not session layer vulnerability?",
      "options": [
        "Mishandling of undefined, poorly defined",
        "Spoofing and hijacking of data based on failed authentication attempts",
        "Passing of session-credentials allowing intercept and unauthorized use",
        "Weak or non-existent authentication mechanisms"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Wofür steht VPN?",
      "options": [
        "Variable Public Network",
        "Virtual Private Tunnel",
        "Virtual Public Tunnel",
        "Vietnam Protocal Network"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Was bedeutet die Abkürzung SSH?",
      "options": [
        "Secure Securer Shell",
        "Secure Shell Hub",
        "Secure Shell"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Welche SSH Keys gibt es?",
      "options": [
        "Open and Secure",
        "Private and Public",
        "Personal and Common"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Wieviele Festplatten werden mindestends für ein RAID 1 System gebraucht?",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "2",
        "5",
        "3"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Was ist eine Maßnahme der Datensicherung",
      "options": [
        "RAID",
        "VPN",
        "Verschlüsselung"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Was ist eine Technik zum Sichern von Passwörter in Datenbanken?",
      "options": [
        "Sugaring",
        "Seasoning",
        "Peppering",
        "Salting"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Welches Verfahren wird bei RAID 0 verwendet?",
      "options": [
        "Flipping",
        "Radonming",
        "Copying",
        "Striping",
        "Mirroring"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Wie TILT ist eigentlich Niclas damit er jetzht die Scheiße machen darf?",
      "options": [
        "FULL TILT",
        "MEDIUM TILT",
        "NO TILT"
      ],
      "correct": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    }
  ]
}
